{
    "subject": "resource/Windows_Server_2003",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Windows Server 2003",
    "human_readable": "The name of Windows Server 2003 is Windows Server 2003.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9861190319061279,
            "question": "What is the name of Windows Server 2003?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.969658613204956,
            "question": "Is 'Windows Server 2003' a version of Microsoft Windows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8910923600196838,
            "question": "When was Windows Server 2003 released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8409451842308044,
            "question": "What type of systems is Windows Server 2003 primarily used for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7836262583732605,
            "question": "Where can I find more information about Windows Server 2003?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7583671808242798,
            "question": "Is Windows Server 2003 still supported by Microsoft?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7551959753036499,
            "question": "What are some key features of Windows Server 2003?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7309468984603882,
            "question": "What are some alternatives to Windows Server 2003?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7153409719467163,
            "question": "How does Windows Server 2003 compare to previous versions of Windows Server?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6729230880737305,
            "question": "Are there any known security vulnerabilities in Windows Server 2003?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Windows Server 2003 is Windows Server 2003.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3208_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Windows Server 2003 compare to previous versions of Windows Server?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3208_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some alternatives to Windows Server 2003?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3208_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key features of Windows Server 2003?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3208_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3208_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3208_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3208_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3208_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3208_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3208_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3208_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3208_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3208_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3208_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to the operating system named \"Windows Server 2003,\" confirming that it is indeed called by this name."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}